<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Axiomize</title>
    <link>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Axiomize</description>
    <image>
      <title>Axiomize</title>
      <url>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Random process contents</title>
      <link>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/posts/rp0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/posts/rp0/</guid>
      <description>Lecture 1 Relative Frequency Interpretation Set Theory Applying Set Theory to Probability Probability Axioms Lecture 2 Conditional Probability Law of Total Probability Bayes Theorem Statistical Independence Bernoulli Trials Reliability Problems Lecture 3 Bernulli trials, Binomial, and Poisson law De Moivre-Laplace Theorem Probability Review Summary Lecture 4 Definitions of Random Variable Examples of Random Variable Cumulative Distribution Function Probability Density Function Probability Mass Function Continuous-Type Random Variables Discrete-Type Random Variables Lecture 5 Two Random Variables Random Vector Complex Random Variable Conditional Distributions/Densities Independence of Random Variables Functions of Random Variables Functions of Random Vectors Lecture 6 Expected Value of a Random Variable Moments of Random Variable Uncorrelated and Orthogonal Random Variables Markov Inequality Chebyshev (Tschebysheff) Inequality Moment Generation Function (MGF) and Characteristic Fuction Characteristic Function for a Random Vector Characteristic Function Example Lecture 7 Conditional Expectation Application of Expectation-Estimation Communication Theory Example Linear minimum mean squared error(LMMSE) estimator LMMSE Estimator from a Random Vector Lecture 8 Expected Value Vector and Matrix Correlation and Covariance Matrix Cross-correlation and Cross-covariance Matrix Univariate Normal Random Variable Bivariate Normal Random Variables Multivariate Normal Random Variables Lecture 9 (pending) Lecture 10 (pending) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/posts/st1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/posts/st1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The amount of information and data that are becoming available to us is growing exponentially. As the amount of available data grows, so is our need to understand it.
If you torture the data long enough. it will confess to anything.
- Ronald Coase
Why statistical literacy is essential in data sceince Statistics provides the skills to access whether the data are sufficient to answer the questions at hand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I&amp;rsquo;m a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s student at Jeonbuk National University, majoring in statistics and minoring in computer science. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in data mining, data visualization, machine and deep learning especially image segmentaion. Nowadays I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a something worth putting my life on the line for.
Awards National Information Society Agency(NIA) - Data Creater Camp Hackathon 2nd award (2021. 09. 04 ~ 2021. 11. 20.)
Jeonbuk Natioanl University - Data Analysis Competition 1st award (2022 01/17 ~ 01/20)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WooHyeok-Moon.github.io/en/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>test en</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
